Hamed Edalati Fard

Summary

For about 22 years, I have been working in the field of information technology in the tax affairs department of Mashhad. My main duties include administrative systems support, data extraction, data analysis and statistical report generation.

In line with the above tasks, I have produced several programs with Delphi, Visual Basic, and PHP languages and using SQL Server and MySQL databases.

Experience

Employee - 2000 to now

Tax Administration, Mashhad

- Support for tax software systems.
- Data extraction, data analysis, presentation of statistical and management reports.
- Teaching and training how to use tax systems.
- Teaching Python to IT colleagues.

Teacher - 2012 to 2016

Payam Noor University, Mashhad & Fariman

• Teaching Network, Internet Engineering and Management Information Systems.

Teacher - 2010 to 2013

University of Applied Science, Mashhad

 Teaching Internet Engineering, Design and Analysis of Systems and Use of Excel in Accounting.

Teacher - 2003 to 2007

Ferdowsi University College, Mashhad

Teaching Internet, Macromedia Flash and Visual Basic.

Education

Master's Degree: Computer Engineering (software)

(2008-2012) Islamic Azad University, Mashhad

Bachelor of Science: Applied mathematics in computers

(1992-1997) Ferdowsi University, Mashhad



Contact

+98 9151232607

hamed.edalati-gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/hamed-edalati-fard

Highlights

- Love to study
- Interested in python
- Continuous learning
- Creativity
- Determined

Skills

Excel

Word	*	*	*	*	*
HTML	*	*	*	*	*
Java Script	*	*	*	*	*
CSS	*	*	*	*	*
Photoshop	*	*	*	*	*
PHP	*	*	*	*	*
My SQL	*	*	*	*	*
SQL Server	*	*	*	*	*
Python	*	*	*	*	*
Git	*	*	*	*	*
Teaching	*	*	*	*	*
English Language	*	*	*	*	*